https://www.annexbusinessmedia.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Statement
At Annex Business Media (Annex), we are committed to a voluntary Privacy Policy. The objective is to ensure that your Personal Information is managed in a responsible and transparent manner.
The privacy of our users is important to us. We request personal information from time to time in order to allow you to participate in various offerings. If you are in a jurisdiction affected by GDPR, we use the minimum information required to pursue the legitimate interests of serving you information relevant to your business or profession while allowing us to generate the revenue required to do so. We are committed to letting you know how we use your Personal Information.
We will keep your Personal Information in secure data storage in order to safeguard it from unauthorized access, it will be kept for as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the identified purposes or as required by law. Should you require that information, or want it destroyed, please contact us here.
We will not share your information with 3rd parties. The only exception will be when we are legally obliged to do so (such as by court order or search warrant) or when you authorize us to do so. Your information will be protected and only disclosed in part to contracted third parties as part of fully-disclosed lead generation campaigns for suppliers or services relevant to your business. In accordance with the Canadian Anti-Spam Law (CASL), in no cases will email addresses be disclosed.
The Information Gathered
At Annex, we want to ensure we deliver information that is relevant to your business needs and interests. We may use a browser feature called a “cookie” to store some Personal Information. This Personal Information identifies your browser to us when you visit our site. You are able to turn this feature off in your browser and continue to use the site. Visit https://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies to find step-by-step instructions on how to do this for your browser. If you decide not to accept cookies you may not be able to use some of the convenience features on our sites.
If we, or one of our partners, hosts a contest or a promotion, it will be your option to enter and your option to provide personal information.
We analyze traffic in aggregate to determine which features and services people use in order to improve our web site. Again, for those in the GDPR zone, this is for the legitimate interest of allowing our editors to provide content that is of the highest value to our aggregate audience. We use Google Analytics on our sites for anonymous reporting of site usage. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics monitoring your behaviour on our sites, please visit this link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
We prepare aggregated user statistics or information summaries in order to describe our services to third parties such as prospective business partners and advertisers and for other lawful purposes. However, our partners will never have direct access to your Personal Information.
We may also use information you have given us to present Web page advertisements or promotions that we hope will be of particular interest to someone in your industry or job function. Some of our advertisers make use of tags and/or anonymous cookies to track how many people have seen a particular ad, or to track how many people have seen it more than once. For more information on how we use Cookies to deliver relevant advertising, and for steps on how to opt-out of seeing these ads, visit: https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads.
Because we do not control any of the means of transmission of your personal data we cannot guarantee that information that you disclose will be kept private. Though we have employed such security features as described above to protect your privacy, we cannot take any responsibility for your use of the Internet to send confidential information.
Emails
Annex Business Media is certified CASL compliant by the Alliance for Audited Media (AAM). As such, we ensure we have the right to share information with you via email, employ simple unsubscribe mechanisms, and offer a detailed subscription preference centre where you can control what, if any, emails you receive. If you have concerns, please contact our CASL Compliance Officer here.
For those in the GDPR zone, we also respect CASL express and implied consent standards in pursuing a legitimate interest to provide you with news and information relevant to your industry in a timely and convenient method. All emails include a functioning and regularly-tested unsubscribe mechanism that takes readers to a detailed user preference centre. That allows you to control precisely what you wish to receive. We do not share emails with any third-party.
Updated: May 2018
Home
About
Values
Brands
Careers
ToolBox
Podcast
